<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JSCKit</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_circumference">Circumference</string>
    <string name="menu_navigation">Navigation</string>
    <string name="menu_me">Me</string>
    <string name="article">
        \u3000\u3000Most parents genuinely do their best to provide their children with a happy and healthy upbringing, but even these individuals can accidentally make mistakes that may result in future therapy appointments.
        \n\u3000\u3000Unfortunately, some parents go beyond the occasional mistake and veer into the toxic category. Regardless of whether or not a parent is purposefully being toxic, there are several behaviors that can cause so much emotional and mental damage to a child that it ends up greatly affecting them even after they have grown up.
        \n\u3000\u3000If you experienced any of the following situations as a child, the odds are high that one or both of your parents were at least slightly toxic.
        \n1. They Fail To Provide You With Affirmation And Security
        \n\u3000\u3000Some people believe that showing tough love is an important way to ensure that their children are able to take care of themselves in the future. If you were the recipient of this approach on a regular basis, you might even believe that this has had a positive impact on your life. However, if you practically fall apart now because of any perceived failure or rejection, then this most likely stems from a parent\'s toxic refusal to provide you with the right amount of security and affirmation while you were young. Tough love might work sometimes, but it cannot be the only approach a parent takes if they want their child to become a well-rounded adult.
        \n2. They Are Overly Critical
        \n\u3000\u3000Everyone\'s parents criticize from time to time. Without this component, we might never learn how to do numerous things properly, such as everyday chores like washing laundry. A toxic parent takes this to extremes by being overly critical about everything their child does. Parents can make the mistake of believing that they do this to make sure their children avoid making costly mistakes. Unfortunately, what this behavior really does is causing the child to develop a harsh inner critic that can be borderline crippling during adulthood.
        \n3. They Demand Your Attention
        \n\u3000\u3000Toxic parents often turn their children into their own parental substitutes by demanding their attention at all times. This can be seen as bonding between the parent and child, but it is really a parasitic relationship that requires too much of the child\'s time and energy when they should be focused on learning other skills. Although it may be difficult at times, a well-rounded parent will allow their children enough space to grow and be kids without demanding constant interaction to suit their own needs.
        \n4. They Make Toxic "Jokes" About You
        \n\u3000\u3000All parents occasionally pick on their children, but when the so-called jokes become commonplace, this can be a huge problem. You do not need to accept this type of behavior just because your parent has always joked about something such as your height or weight. Ultimately, this is an undermining tactic that can make you feel very badly about yourself. If a parent has a legitimate concern to address with their child, they should be honest and non-critical, as opposed to making mean jokes.
        \n5. They Cause You To Justify Terrible Behavior
        \n\u3000\u3000Did you grow up believing that your parent was physically or emotionally abusive to you because you deserved it? If so, you may still be justifying the terrible behavior of others at your own expense. Toxic parents can twist any situation to suit their needs, and this leaves children with two choices: accept that their parent is wrong or internalize all of the blame. In most cases, children, even those who are adults now, choose the latter option.
        \n6. They Do Not Allow You To Express Negative Emotions
        \n\u3000\u3000Parents who refuse to nurture their child\'s emotional needs and make light of their negative emotions are setting up a future where the child will feel unable to express what they need. There is nothing wrong with helping children see the positive side of any situation. However, being completely dismissive of a child\'s negative feelings and emotional needs can lead to depression and make it more difficult for them to appropriately handle negativity as adults.
    </string>
</resources>
